Garet Lam

Web Developer

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Experienced Web Developer with passion for creating attractive and interactive websites meeting customer needs and exceeding expectations. Excels in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and PHP development. Well-versed in developing custom WordPress ecommerce solutions and delivering quickly to clients. Works at fast pace to meet tight deadlines. Enthusiastic team player ready to contribute to company success.

WORK HISTORY

Web Developer - Tranxactor

Oct 2021 - Present

- Planned website development and designs, converting mockups into usable web presence with Next.js, React, Typescript, ShadCN, Wordpress PHP and Tailwind CSS with CMS implementation (Strapi).
- Projects developed: Subway Rewards Gamification, MyJournal Loyalty Rewards for Columbus Coffee & Farro, eGift Merchant PWA, i-PAY Remittance site. PayZe, Kupid Web Admin (POS System), transactional & promotional emails for 20+ retailers
- Designed and developed user interfaces, translating visual concepts into fully functional, responsive code
- Created promotional assets for social media and existing websites (Adobe Suite)

Web Developer (Intern) - National Institute for Health Innovation

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

- Developed a COVID Evaluation App using Drupal CMS with Twig (PHP)
- Developed a Chronic Pancreatis App using Quasar Framework (VueJS) for deployment to web as a PWA

Project Manager / Graphic Design - Photoshack Ltd

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

- Started as a graphic designer creating promotional and web content
- Assisted with redesigning the website & translating it to code
- Managed new projects and task delegation

EDUCATION

Mission Ready HQ - Advanced Software Development

- Developed applications using Cloud Services such as AWS and Azure. Includes Al, Cloud, Frontend, Backend, and DevOps technologies.

Auckland University of Technology - Bachelor of Digital Design

- Digital Asset Creation such as 3D Web Models and animation

CONTACT:

32 Whakatupu Rd, Flat Bush, 2019 gartoyou@gmail.com +64220473697

PORTFOLIO:

gar212.github.io

TECH STACK:

- React
- TypeScript
- PHP
- Next.JS
- Vite
- Wordpress
- Git
- Node.JS
- Tailwind CSS
- ShadCN
- AWS
- Woocommerce
- Elementor

CREATIVES:

- Photoshop
- Illustrator
- Indesign
- Figma

INTERESTS AND HOBBIES:

- Photography
- Art
- Graphic Design